[
    {
      "question": "What is our instructor Charlie’s dog’s name?",
      "correctAnswer": "Beau",
      "answer2": "Bruce",
      "answer3": "Wanda",
      "answer4": "Hemingsworth"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is our instructor Charlie’s dog’s name?",
        "correctAnswer": "Beau",
        "answer2": "Bruce",
        "answer3": "Wanda",
        "answer4": "Hemingsworth"
      },
      {
        "question": "What country is Machu Picchu in?",
        "correctAnswer": "Peru",
        "answer2": "Chile",
        "answer3": "Colombia",
        "answer4": "Brazil"
      },
      {
        "question": "What is one of Charlie’s cat’s names?",
        "correctAnswer": "Bitcoin",
        "answer2": "Git",
        "answer3": "Handlebars",
        "answer4": "Java"
      },
      {
        "question": "What is Sir Isaac Newton known for?",
        "correctAnswer": "Developing the law of gravity",
        "answer2": "Discovering electricity",
        "answer3": "Lead singer of Metallica",
        "answer4": "Was a knight of the Round Table"
      },
      {
        "question": "What is Bruce Banner’s superhero name?",
        "correctAnswer": "Hulk",
        "answer2": "Iron Man",
        "answer3": "Dr. Strange",
        "answer4": "Vision"
      },
      {
        "question": "What year did NASA first land astronauts on the moon?",
        "correctAnswer": "1969",
        "answer2": "1959",
        "answer3": "1960",
        "answer4": "1690"
      },
      {
        "question": "How many species of whales are there?",
        "correctAnswer": "90",
        "answer2": "10",
        "answer3": "50",
        "answer4": "200"
      },
      {
        "question": "Which movie did Quentin Tarantino NOT direct?",
        "correctAnswer": "Die Hard",
        "answer2": "Pulp Fiction",
        "answer3": "Kill Bill",
        "answer4": "Django Unchained"
      },
      {
        "question": "Who was Indira Gandhi?",
        "correctAnswer": "First female prime minister of India",
        "answer2": "Social media influencer",
        "answer3": "Inventor of programmable computer",
        "answer4": "Famous architect"
      },
      {
        "question": "Rickrolling refers to a song by what musician?",
        "correctAnswer": "Rick Astley",
        "answer2": "Ric Ocasek",
        "answer3": "Richard Nixon",
        "answer4": "Richie Rich"
      },
      {
        "question": "What site is known for job postings?",
        "correctAnswer": "Indeed",
        "answer2": "Monsters Inc",
        "answer3": "LinkedOut",
        "answer4": "Discord"
      },
      {
        "question": "Where are the Olympics being held in 2021?",
        "correctAnswer": "Tokyo",
        "answer2": "Los Angeles",
        "answer3": "Switzerland",
        "answer4": "Rio"
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the largest lake in the U.S.?",
        "correctAnswer": "Superior",
        "answer2": "Erie",
        "answer3": "Ontario",
        "answer4": "Michigan"
      },
      {
        "question": "What animal is the Cheetos mascot?",
        "correctAnswer": "Cheetah",
        "answer2": "Orangutan",
        "answer3": "Gecko",
        "answer4": "Tiger"
      },
      {
        "question": "What year was Swedish environmental activist Greta Thunberg born?",
        "correctAnswer": "2003",
        "answer2": "1993",
        "answer3": "1973",
        "answer4": "1963"
      },
      {
        "question": "Who wrote 'The Hill We Climb' and is the youngest inaugural poet in U.S. history?",
        "correctAnswer": "Amanda Gorman",
        "answer2": "Maya Angelou",
        "answer3": "Macaulay Culkin",
        "answer4": "Robert Downey Jr."
      },
      {
        "question": "Pediatricians recommend a maximum of how many hours of screen time per day for children?",
        "correctAnswer": "2 hours",
        "answer2": "Unlimited",
        "answer3": "16 hours if including YouTube time",
        "answer4": "Half an hour"
      },
      {
        "question": "What’s an example of a palindrome?",
        "correctAnswer": "Kayak",
        "answer2": "Tacos for cats",
        "answer3": "Camel",
        "answer4": "Beep"
      },
      {
        "question": "What is myopia?",
        "correctAnswer": "Nearsightedness",
        "answer2": "Low-grade fever",
        "answer3": "Sleep disorder",
        "answer4": "Charlie's cat's name"
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the default name of the main character in Minecraft?",
        "correctAnswer": "Steve",
        "answer2": "Joe",
        "answer3": "Karen",
        "answer4": "Roger"
      }
  ]
  
